<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>~/seanbowers.tech</title>
        <link>https://seanbowers.tech/</link>
        <description>~/seanbowers.tech</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Sean Bowers</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:08:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://seanbowers.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>How to Make a Subnetting Cheat Sheet</title>
    <link>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/how-to-make-a-subnetting-cheat-sheet/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:08:50 -0700</pubDate><author>
                    <name>Sean Bowers</name>
                </author><guid>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/how-to-make-a-subnetting-cheat-sheet/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[How to Make a Subnetting Cheat Sheet First, write out the decimal representation of each bit of a single 8bit byte.
128 64 32 16 8 4 2 1 Next, we want to subtract the bit decimal value from 256.
256 256 256 256 256 256 256 256 -128 -64 -32 -16 -8 -4 -2 -1 128 192 224 240 248 252 254 255 This gives us our &ldquo;magic number,&rdquo; as some people call it, as well as the remaining bits of our network from the default subnet mask.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>The Joys of Subnetting</title>
    <link>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/the-joys-of-subnetting/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:37:54 -0700</pubDate><author>
                    <name>Sean Bowers</name>
                </author><guid>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/the-joys-of-subnetting/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have been studying for my CompTIA Network+ certification exam. This is the one of the early career trifecta (A+, Network+, &amp; Security+) that I had been hoping to avoid. I was hoping that I might be able to find a cybersecurity track job without needing the Network+, so I could forego that exam entirely. Now the exam itself may not be a necessary for getting into cybersecurity, however understanding networking in general is absolutely necessary.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Raspberry Pi Woes</title>
    <link>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/raspberry-pi-woes/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 23:01:32 -0700</pubDate><author>
                    <name>Sean Bowers</name>
                </author><guid>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/raspberry-pi-woes/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I had five days off—two for a wedding, two for my regular weekend, and the 4th of July. I decided that this would be a great time to finally migrate my Nextcloud to my new Raspberry Pi case, the (Argon One)[https://argon40.com/products/argon-one-m-2-case-for-raspberry-pi-4] . I was excited to pull my personal cloud off of (Digital Ocean)[https://www.digitalocean.com/] and into my home. That is not to say that I wasn&rsquo;t pleased with the service they have at Digital Ocean, I actually enjoyed my time there quite a bit.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Fresh Fruit for Rotting Vegetables</title>
    <link>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/fresh-fruit-for-rotting-vegetables/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 23:27:16 -0700</pubDate><author>
                    <name>Sean Bowers</name>
                </author><guid>https://seanbowers.tech/posts/fresh-fruit-for-rotting-vegetables/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[While I have never been a diehard Dead Kennedys fan, I have always loved their use of linguistic cacophony, hence the title. Basically, I have been building and rebuilding, building and rebuilding this website for quite sometime now. I am using Hugo for ease of use, as opposed to writing HTML, CSS, and JS for every single post. I can just tell Hugo to spin me up a markdown file, where I write my text, load it with links and images if need be, and then ask it to build HTML and CSS from my markdown given the predefined parameters.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
